adfonic.com 2011-03-07

# Privacy policy | Mobile advertising | Adfonic

This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the use of the Internet and any other electronic communications networks by Adfonic Limited. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us at **privacy[at]adfonic[dot]com**.

**Information collected**

We collect personal information from visitors to this web site through the use of online forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake, including partial details of payment cards used, which we use for identification, but in no case do we retain your whole credit card number.

We collect additional information automatically about your visit to our web site.

**Use of personal information**

We process personal information collected via this web site for the purposes of:

  1. providing and personalising our services;

  2. dealing with your enquiries and requests;

  3. administering orders and accounts relating to our suppliers or customers;

  4. administering membership records;

  5. crime prevention and prosecution of offenders;

  6. fundraising;

  7. maintaining information as a reference tool or general resource;

  8. carrying out market research campaigns; and

  9. providing you with information about products and services.

We may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individuals are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes.

**Use of cookies**

We use cookies to identify you when you visit this web site and to keep track of your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile.

Our use of cookies also allows registered users to be presented with a personalised version of the site, carry out transactions and have access to information about their account.

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However, switching off cookies will restrict your use of our web site.

**Disclosures**

We will only disclose personal information to other companies within our group of companies, business partners, government bodies and law enforcement agencies successors in title to our business and suppliers we engage to process data on our behalf.

If you are a Publisher, we may include your business' name in our marketing materials, unless you request otherwise in writing. 

**Other web sites**

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

**Access right**

You have a right to access the personal data held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please write to us at 31 Davies Street, London, W1K 4LP, United Kingdom.

**Internet-based transfers**

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this web site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.
